{
    "id": "6ab143038cab436ca7cb1560a2248f4f",
    "title": "Gap Filling Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I have ……………………. doubts.",
            "description": "Use a few to refer to a small number.",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "a few",
                "the few"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6ab2df437b8c4a2bada36053949623fc"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is junior ………………………… me.",
            "description": "Use to after junior, senior, inferior, superior etc. ",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "fe38adcc51df4c8aac77d1d827f5c249"
        },
        {
            "question": "No other language is  ……………………….. as Chinese.",
            "description": "Use the positive adjective in the construction as...as...",
            "answers": [
                "as difficult",
                "more difficult",
                "most difficult"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3c03dc0f98bd48318243334d644e9d05"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is ……………………. than that.",
            "description": "Cheaper is the comparative form of cheap.",
            "answers": [
                "more cheap",
                "cheaper",
                "more cheaper"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "36fa8dde7d9849638136a660e4cd4fe6"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… knowledge is always a dangerous thing.",
            "description": "A little indicates a small quantity. ",
            "answers": [
                "Little",
                "A little",
                "The little"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9d859818f7344fd8a2418fd9b88e7a80"
        },
        {
            "question": "Of the two routes, this is ……………………………",
            "description": "The comparative is used to speak of two things. ",
            "answers": [
                "shorter",
                "the shorter",
                "the shortest"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f8ca412ab75d4d738a50c9d9873a698a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have ……………………… knowledge of politics.",
            "description": "Little knowledge means almost no knowledge. ",
            "answers": [
                "little",
                "the little",
                "few"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5c7979a8b0c848e0b2d3e66dba7e36b0"
        },
        {
            "question": "This material is superior ……………………………… that.",
            "description": "Use to instead of than after superior, inferior etc.",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "to",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "48360cfd27d841598d526672335ff7ba"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ……………………………… of the three brothers.",
            "description": "The superlative is used to compare one person or thing with the whole group to which they belong. ",
            "answers": [
                "older",
                "the older",
                "the oldest",
                "oldest"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b32b00ac08af4dc9abb7946b9e3815ed"
        },
        {
            "question": "We are not as rich as ……………………………",
            "description": "Object pronouns are more common after as and than.",
            "answers": [
                "they",
                "them"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "94a883d5471d43d7be39029e8d5a5edc"
        },
        {
            "question": "Man is …………………………… animal.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "the most intelligent",
                "most intelligent",
                "the more intelligent"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cb9bccae2e1246a3b0e4a7630d162ce3"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………….. Indians speak English.",
            "description": "Use many before a noun without a determiner. ",
            "answers": [
                "Many",
                "Many of"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "189b7983d2ec4d7392423f2d01657302"
        }
    ]
}